question_data = [
    {"category": "Animals",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Ceratosaurus, a dinosaur known for having a horn on the top of "
                 "its nose, is also known to be a decendent of the Tyrannosaurus "
                 "Rex.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Seoul is the capital of North Korea.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Chevrolet Corvette has always been made exclusively with V8 engines only.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive "
                 "every tweet by American citizens.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Japanese god Izanagi successfully returned his wife Izanami from the Underworld.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Blue Danube was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
